

CONTACTO

- +34 655 661558
- jesusmunozpost@gmail.com
- C/ Doctor Esquerdo 120, 28007, Madrid, España
- in linkedin.com/in/jesús-muñoz-post
- Jesus Munnoz. github.io

EDUCATION

Codenotch

Bootcamp Full stack web developer.

mar. 2024 - oct. 2024

Universidad Camilo José Cela

Diseño y desarrollo de videojuegos

2012 - 2016

Universidad Francisco de Vitoria

Imagen para el diagnóstico 2008 - 2010

SKILLS

- Angular (HTML5 || CSS || TypeScript)
- JavaScript || Node.js.
- Figma || Canva.
- Kanban.
- C || C plus plsu || C#
- Inglés (C1) || Español (Native)

Jesús Muñoz Post

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a friendly and hardworking junior web developer.
I am passionate about interface design, which is why I pursued a degree in Video Game Design and Development, specializing in UX/UI. I have just completed a Full Stack Web Bootcamp, learning the latest technologies in the field.

I have experience in understanding user needs, allowing me to develop more user-friendly and easy-to-use apps and tools.

I'm just starting out, and I hope to have the opportunity to learn from the best in the field and become one of them.

EXPERIENCE

Junior Web developer

Jul. 2024 - Sep. 2024

Codenotch

- Sketches, functionality, and initial design developed in Figma.
- Front end developed using Angular (HTML5, CSS, TypeScript)
- Back end developed using Node.js y JavaScript.
- Database developed using MySQL Workbench

Analista de desarrollo May. 2023 - Nov. 2023

Carrefour

Back end developer using C.

Clinical Application Specialist Jul. 2021 - May. 2023

Align Technology

CAD Designer Oct. 2018 - Jul. 2021

Align Technology

Unity 3D Developer Nov. 2017 - Oct. 2018

Tecnatom